A sound soul dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
I have come to strike a bargain.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
I'm falling down to my eyes.
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby.
Out of my baby.
Oh no.
I'm falling down.
Black, red, brown, brown
信じてくれたなら
When you lost it were young
Forever with your soul
見上がれば輝く
月のように
メデューザ
She's here
Even with her soul protect on I can tell
That's her behind this door
Medusa
There's someone there
I'm so thirsty
Maybe I could have a glass of water
Witch
Medusa
There's a little girl at the door
Is there something I can do for you?
You did this
I don't understand what you mean
Whatever did I do?
It's because of you that Crona's suffering so much
Oh my, so Crona's a friend of yours?
Tell me, how's he doing?
How do you think he's doing?
You was like this by his own mother
Oh, I've been very worried about him
He's always been such a fragile child, you see
How could you do this to him?
You call yourself a parent?
Do you think I could see Crona?
A mother shouldn't be separated from her child for so long
Would you drop the act?
Of course I'm not sure how he'll react
Seeing me in such a sad state like this
I told you, drop the act!
Calm down, Maka, breathe
Let's get out of here
It's useless anyway
Talking to someone like her won't get you anywhere
Do you hear me, Medusa?
You're gonna spend the rest of your life in that dark little cell
Enjoy, it's more than you deserve
Come on
Sorry, children, but I'm afraid it's not going to end like this
Don't you agree?
Professor Stein
The cards are cut
Medusa surrenders to the DWMA?
Yeah, now that was a bit of a shock, huh?
We were all convinced that Medusa was dead
And then she waltzes up to the Academy and surrenders?
It's my fault
I was certain that Stein and I had finished her off for good in that battle
Don't forget, we're dealing with a witch here
With them, anything's possible
And that's just the beginning
Medusa's no ordinary witch
We can't handle her using ordinary means
Why did you come here?
To see you, of course
Did you think they'd let you walk out of here whenever you want?
The world has begun to move, Stein
You feel it, I know you do
Besides, you know I'd never bet on something I wasn't guaranteed to win
We'll see, won't we?
Are you feeling all right, Stein?
Your voice is trembling a bit
I can hardly bear this, watching as the madness slowly consumes you
Don't you have other things to worry about right now?
How could I not be worried?
I need you
Are you ready to join me?
You aren't telling the whole truth
You must have had another motive besides talking to me
You have to learn to free yourself from the rules
Otherwise you'll never be saved
Come over to my side
Together we'll make things happen
We'll see the dawn of a new world
It's time, Stein
You know that, don't you?
Terribly sorry
Am I interrupting?
Get out of here, Stein
You know you shouldn't leave your lab right now
You're coming with me
Let's go
Now where are you taking me?
Let me guess, to an interrogation room?
Well, am I right?
Please, mister
Why am I all tied up like this?
My arms hurt and I can barely breathe
Give it up
I'm not falling for it
Oh?
You talked to me though, didn't you?
So I won that round
Pretty soon you're gonna be the one doing the talking
Now then
Shall we get started?
Torture's a bad idea
Oh, you can do it, of course
But you should think carefully before hurting my body
Or didn't you realize that this body was borrowed?
Damn her
She's thought of everything, hasn't she?
As a parent you should show some sympathy
That child deserves her body back
I only need it until my magic fully recovers
It's alone
I'll give it back sometime
Just when we thought you couldn't sink lower
You might want to be more careful in how you speak to me
You don't even know what I've come here to offer
I could be the saving grace you need
Oh, yeah?
I have certain information that could prove useful to the Academy
Information?
Take me to the Reaper and we'll talk, otherwise you get nothing
Don't be ridiculous
You're in no position to make demands
Anyway, you aren't exactly trustworthy
Why should we believe anything you have to say?
I was afraid it would come to this
If that's your attitude, I suppose I'll just have to make you believe
I was good with a shovel back when I was alive, too
I was that kind of man
I don't mind all the digging
But what could Medusa be hiding here?
This looks like...
Brew
We ran all the tests
This is the real Brew
She gave it to you in order to convince you to let her speak with me directly?
She's insisting on it
Apparently she wants to make a deal with us
A deal, huh?
I've got no damn clue what that witch has up her sleeve
Why is she willing to give up Brew to us this easily?
And how did she get her hands on it?
There's a lot about this we don't understand
I don't know what she's up to
But one thing we can count on
She wants to use us somehow
I'm sure of that
At any rate, she's right
I do think I should speak with her in person
Are you sure?
Yes
I want you to bring her here immediately
So?
Grim Reaper
Yeah, yeah
You're enjoying yourself immensely, aren't you?
Because of you, the world is now on the brink of total disaster
That may be true
But I'd still like to show you my gratitude for speaking with me
Hmm
Let's get to the point
First there's the matter of these restraints
Perhaps you could remove them
They are quite uncomfortable
And surely with you standing right there, they aren't really necessary
Don't play with me
If you wanted those restraints off, you could have removed them yourself a long time ago
But it would be meaningless if I took them off myself
Hmm
Ugh
Don't try anything
I won't think twice about ripping you apart
REAPER CHOP
Um, your death, sir?
Oh, come on
After all she's done, she deserves at least one chop
Okay
The Reaper chop
That's the thing I hated most about the academy
Even when I was the school nurse, I lived in fear of that chop
It's awful
Come here
Now
What deal were you talking about?
My bloomers are showing
Huh?
He's treating me like a child
I miscalculated
Excuse me, Reaper
Could you put me down?
Bloomers! Adorable!
My mucca wore those when she was little
So sweet little baby bloomers
This is getting too weird
I need to get them to focus somehow
Now if we could return to the topic we were discussing
Here's a question
What do you think bloomers would look like on a grown woman?
It's been done
Centuries ago
They used to wear them all the time
Ugh
But if they did it now
Wouldn't it be a bit creepy?
A philosophical discussion on women's underwear
That's enough!
Stop it right now!
Oh
We shouldn't talk about this in front of a lady
That's not what I was concerned about!
Right
Now about this deal of yours
No, put me down right now!
I don't promise again!
If you don't stop that, I'm going to kill you
What's her problem?
Can't she even take a little joke?
And it was expertly executed too
Repetition is the foundation of humor
Three times as best
Absolutely, I agree
However, since we were interrupted
We'll have to start from the beginning now
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Oh, come back!
I won't pick you up by the hood anymore
Is that a promise?
What do you say, Reaper?
The conditions of the deal are fair
If anything, I think you're getting the better end of the bargain
What I'm offering is the answer to the question weighing heaviest on your mind right now
We won't agree to a thing until we hear your conditions
Fine, if you don't want to tell us, I'll pick you up by the hood again
Hey, you promised!
Sweet adorable bloomers!
Quit that already, it's creepy
Just put me down, I'll explain the deal, but let me go
You honestly call yourselves adults?
As for what I have to offer
Will the Kishin's location do?
Hmm, you're lying
We put all our effort into finding him
And we haven't uncovered a single trace
Death Scythe has a point there
How can we be sure you aren't lying?
Can you prove what you say is true?
No, I can't
At least not while I still don't have your complete trust
Is that so?
Alright then, give us the location
We'll check and see if it's true
You can't really think I'd be stupid enough to do that
Why not?
If I tell, what's your incentive to keep your end of the deal?
What is our end of the deal?
It's not that complicated, really
I want to be released from Academy custody immediately
I'll also expect you to guarantee my safety, of course
That's all you want?
Yes, that's all of it
Hmm
Unfortunately, I don't believe that's a condition we can accept
That's too bad
I suppose this means you'd rather live under the thumb of arachnophobia
Than let little old me go
What's this?
What do you mean by that?
Are you saying that arachnophobia and the Kishin are working together?
You'll know soon enough, won't you?
No
It's alright
it's all right as long as I'm here nothing can hurt you
and I won't ever leave your side
I'll stay here and protect you from everything you fear
I promise I will keep you safe
rest easy it's all right
mosquito yes activating moral manipulation right now
so
what's that it looks like it's begun
what's happening what's begun please explain
Arachne has allied herself with Asherah she's harnessed his madness and she hopes to spread
it throughout the entire world well this is too bad for you Medusa thanks to this looks like the
bargains off really why the madness wavelength he's giving off is huge locating the source of it
won't be difficult at all I'm afraid you're wrong that would be impossible what is that
Arachne has set up those relay stations to bounce the wavelength all over the world there's no way
to tell for sure which one of them is the ultimate source you can investigate them one by one but
unless you get lucky you'll be too late you've heard my conditions Reaper what now do we have a deal
oh I'll need a moment there's a lot in this deal I have to consider
it's clear what Medusa is trying to do she wants to instigate a battle between her two rivals
Arachnophobia and the DWMA she knows that if that happens all I can do is sit here and watch the fight
I can't leave Death City that sounds like something she'd plan all right whatever the case if we let
things stand as they are now it would mean disaster so what are we supposed to do that's what I'm trying
to decide do we use her information to wipe out Asherah and Arachne both at the same time or do we take
this opportunity to eliminate Medusa once and for all it's going to be okay they'd be insane to turn
down the offer I just made them it's a simple decision I've won I know it
but if I'm wrong what will they do
they're here
Medusa
you're free to go
hmm
what's happening something wrong come here Maka of all people I think you should see what's happening down
there you'll understand um excuse me coming through please
Medusa hey what the hell's going on here I don't know the details but right now it seems the Academy
has made a deal with Medusa but why that's something I'd be very interested to know too
don't worry about it Maka this isn't the last we'll see of her we still have plenty of time just wait
for it I'm gonna beat the crap out of her and you'll get your chance at her too I'll let you land one on
her face
a deal what is my dad thinking
why are they letting her go it's wrong well done well done Reaper you and your Academy are now my
god
Stein what are you sitting here in the dark
Stein
Stein!
And on that night, Professor Stein disappeared.
나무部分作曲も喔
ザラ好的詞 going on
解菖 Spirituality
渇ñas czk Andong
叩いた口輪 イタツく太陽に
含されて 溢れる涙
Thank you.
Professor, where are you? Professor!
Quick quiz. Here's the first question.
Where is Professor Stein?
A. Out buying groceries,
B. Getting drinks with my dad,
or C. On vacation?
Uh, C.
Correct. So in the next episode, everything will be back to normal again.
You're lying.
Yes, of course I am.
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
Twirl Round and Round,
a new world in which the doc dances?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.